我是石豆瑞小姐,請大家記得按讚打開小鈴鐺喔!
I am Miss Shidourui. Please remember to like and subscribe by clicking the bell icon!
現在,讓我們透過對話的例子來展現這五個步驟在產品開發中的實際應用吧!
Now, let's demonstrate the practical application of these five steps in product development through an example conversation.
在手機購物網站App的產品開發部門中,產品經理大R、產品開發人員小A和小C正在討
論如何提升產品的競爭力。
In the product development department of the mobile shopping website app, Product Manager Big R, and product developers Little A and Little C are discussing how to enhance the competitiveness of the product.
大R首先提出,我們必須站在使用者的角度思考,找出他們的真正需求和問題。
Big R proposed first that we must think from the perspective of the users, in order to identify their true needs and problems.
小A隨後分享他所進行的使用者訪談結果。
"A few moments later, A shared the results of the user interviews that he had conducted."
根據我對使用者的訪談,我發現他們真正需要的是一個簡單易用的操作介面,
Based on my interviews with the users, I found that what they really need is a simple and user-friendly interface.
因為他們覺得能夠快速找到需要購買的產品項目的功能很重要。
Because they consider the ability to quickly locate the desired products for purchase to be important.
大R聽完後提出問題,既然如此,那我們如何簡化操作介面讓使用者更容易上手呢?
After listening to what you said, one question arises: How can we simplify the interface to make it easier for users to get started?
小C和小A隨後提出解決方案。
Xiao C and Xiao A subsequently proposed a solution.
我們可以進行功能的大項目分類,並利用選項的大小來凸顯出重點功能,
We can classify the major projects by functionality and highlight key functions by their significance.
這樣可以讓使用者更直覺地找到他們需要的功能。
This can allow users to find the features they need more intuitively.
大R點頭稱讚道,我認同這些提議,接下來我們將根據這些想法製作兩種不同的產品原型,
然後進行測試。
Da R nodded and praised, "I agree with these suggestions. Next, we will develop two different product prototypes based on these ideas and then proceed with testing."
收集使用者的反饋,並根據反饋進行優化。
Collect user feedback and optimize based on the feedback.
我們也需要持續關注市場趨勢和使用者需求的變化,以確保我們購物網站App產品的競爭
力和吸引力。
We also need to continue to monitor market trends and changes in user demands to ensure the competitiveness and attractiveness of our online shopping app product.
透過這樣的過程,團隊成員以使用者的角度尋找真實需求,強調以人為中心的重要性,
Through this process, team members seek real needs from the perspective of users, emphasizing the importance of a people-centric approach.
並激發團隊創新,找到解決方法,幫助團隊創造出更加符合市場需求和使用者期望的產品。
And stimulate team innovation, find solutions, and help the team create products that better meet market demands and user expectations.
這就是設計思考在產品開發中的實際應用。
This is the practical application of design thinking in product development.